ACWA Photographs 5743 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Dignitaries: Group Pictures of Labor Leaders (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Dignitaries: Margarita Talavera, Chayo Parra - Strikers (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Dignitaries: Mr. and Mrs. Portillo (strikers) with various union officials (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Empty (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Dignitaries: Sargent Shriver (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Dignitaries: Farah Strikers Self-help Activities (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Dignitaries: Misc. (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Dignitaries: Misc. (Box 52, Folder 10)
- International (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Meetings- ACWA Convention (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Meetings- AFL-CIO (Industrial Union Department) 10th Constitutional Convention (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Meetings- AFSCME, DC 37 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Meetings- IAM Convention, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- Meetings- Tel-Aviv, Israel (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Meetings, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  August, 1972.
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 4)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 5)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 6)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 8)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 9)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 10)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 11)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 12)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 13)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 15)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 16)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 17)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 18)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 19)
- Meetings (Box 53, Folder 20)
- Meetings- Misc. (Box 53, Folder 21)
- Farah Workers (Box 53, Folder 22)
- People v. Willie Farah (The Making of) (Box 53, Folder 22a)
- Picketing- Alabama. Andalusia, Taylor Shop, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- Picketing- California (Box 53, Folder 24)
- Picketing- Connecticut (Box 53, Folder 25)
- Picketing- District of Columbia (Box 53, Folder 26)
- Picketing- Georgia (Box 53, Folder 27)
- Picketing- Illinois (Box 53, Folder 28)
- Picketing- Indiana (Box 53, Folder 29)
- Picketing- Louisiana (Box 53, Folder 30)
- Picketing- Maine (Box 53, Folder 31)
- Picketing- Maryland (Box 54, Folder 1)
- Picketing- Massachusetts (Box 54, Folder 2)
- Picketing- Michigan (Box 54, Folder 3)
- Picketing- Minnesota (Box 54, Folder 4)
- Picketing- Mississippi (Box 54, Folder 5)
- Picketing- Missouri (Box 54, Folder 6)
- Picketing- Montana (Box 54, Folder 7)
- Picketing- New Jersey (Box 54, Folder 8)
- Picketing- New York (Box 54, Folder 9)
- Picketing- New York (Box 54, Folder 10)
- Picketing- Ohio (Box 54, Folder 11)
- Picketing- Oregon (Box 54, Folder 12)
- Picketing- Pennsylvania (Box 54, Folder 13)
- Picketing- Pennsylvania (Box 54, Folder 14)
- Picketing- Pennsylvania (Box 54, Folder 15)
- Picketing- Rhode Island (Box 54, Folder 16)
- Picketing- South Carolina (Box 54, Folder 17)
- Picketing- Tennessee (Box 54, Folder 18)
- Picketing- Tennessee (Box 54, Folder 19)
- Picketing- Tennessee (Box 55, Folder 1)
- Picketing- Texas (Box 55, Folder 2)
- Picketing- Washington (Box 55, Folder 3)
- Picketing- Wisconsin (Box 55, Folder 4)
- Picketing- Misc. documents (Box 55, Folder 5)
- Picketing- Misc. stores (Box 55, Folder 6)
- Picketing- Misc. stores (Box 55, Folder 7)
- Picketing- Unknown (Box 55, Folder 8)
- Misc. (Box 55, Folder 9)
- Misc. documents (Box 55, Folder 10)
- V. Alvano, P. Arnone, J. Bell, D. Belanca, H. Block, R. Block, B. Blumberg, H. Blumberg (Box 56, Folder 1)
- J. Borys, M. Brandwen, S. Brandzel, R. Brazier, E. Burdo, J. Catalaanotti, A. Chatman, S. Cohen, G. Dickason, T. DiLauro (Box 56, Folder 2)
- J. Cohen, C. English, C. Ervin, Freedman, H. Frumererman, M. Gassman, S. Genis, E. Grandinetti, A. Hartman, E. Hawes (Box 56, Folder 3)
- S. Hillman, L. Hollander, P. Horton, J. Kroll, S. Levin, D. Jones (Box 56, Folder 4)
- L. Krzycki, L. Levy, P. Licastro, C. Linenberg, J. Lipshutz, F. Lowther, M. Mann, A.D. Marimpietri, E. McGill, S. Levin (Box 56, Folder 5)
- A. Miller, V. Miller, D. Monas, F. Napolitano, S. Nocella, J. Penn, B. Peppercorn, E. Peterson (Box 56, Folder 6)
- A.G. Pipenhagen, J. Potofsky. D. Dubinsky (Box 56, Folder 7)
- J. Potofsky, E. Rabkin, C. Rosen, F. Rosenblum (Box 56, Folder 8)
- F. Rosenblum, Shop scenes (Box 56, Folder 9)
- J. Salerno, J. Schlossberg, S. Skala, S. Spivak, G. Strebel, C. Weinstein, V. Wertheimer, C. Daley (Box 57, Folder 1)
- Banks and Banking, ACWA-NY; Facilities; Community Aid, Foreign; Convention ACWA (1914,1924,1936, 1946); Education and Regional Activities (Cincinnati 1948, Laundry Workers Joint Board 1947, Shirt and Leisurewear Joint Board 1947, South 1947); Factories, 1914-1847 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- Factory Workers; General Executive Board 1915; Health Center- NY, Rehabilitation; Housing- NY, Amalgamated dwellings and interior (Box 57, Folder 3)
- Imports- Canada, NY, Alexanders, General Demonstration (March 19, 1970); Labor Day, 1942; Management Relations (arbitration, Hart-Schaffner-Marx, signing); National Geographic Divisions- Israel; Organizing- historical, 1942-1970 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- Organizing (South, Southwest); Political Action- Presidential, Voter Registration (Box 57, Folder 5)
- Political Action- Voter Turnout, Legislation (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Recreation- arts, music, social, sports; Recreation Centers; Social and Environmental Issues; Strikes, 1930-1949 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- Strikes, Baltimore, Boss Gloves, Canada, 1970-1979 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- Strikes. Chicago, Haggar Slacks, Laundry, Minnesota, Newberry Garment Co. (Box 58, Folder 2)
- Strikes. New York, Ricestix, Shirt Makers, Other Unions (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Union Label- Boycotts, Costumes, Publicity; World War II, ACWA War effort, rallies; Workers- Clothing Industry, contemporary, historical, 1945-1969 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- Workers. Clothing industry - historical, men and women; handicapped, laundry industry including Dollie Lowther Robinson (Box 58, Folder 5)
- Envelope, 2002 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- McGill, Eula, John Dean, Clyde Ware, Albert Cox, 1934 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- McGill, Eula, Polly Brown, Mrs. George Stevens, Bill Adcock, Mollie Down (Box 59, Folder 3)
- McGill, Eula (Box 59, Folder 4)
- McGill, Eula (Box 60)
  Includes Eileen Berry, Eula McGill, and Flossie Whitaker. Local 95, La Follette, TN. 1948. Photographer Fred Hess & Son Atlantic City, NJ.; Professional portraits of Eula McGill ca 1965; J.C. Cooper. 1936. Photographer Lollar's Birmingham, AL; Car decorat
- Local 2, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Local 5, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- Local 6, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Local 11, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Local 11, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Local 17, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Local 17, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Local 17, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- Local 24 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Local 24, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Local 24, 2001 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Local 34 and 38 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- Local 74, 1998 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Local 75, 1997 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Local 75, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- Local 75, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- Local 75, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- Local 100, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- Local 100, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- Local 100, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- Local 226 (Box 61, Folder 21)
- Local 483, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 22)
- Local 814 (Box 61, Folder 23)
- Local 814, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 24)
- some photos removed and put into box 65 (Box 62)
  - Local 63, Officers and Executive Board, 1956 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- New York Joint Board Photos + Certificates - (Box 63)
  - Local 25, Officers and Delegates, 1937 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- Steerage Deck SS Pennland:- (Box 64, Folder 1)
  moved from box 9, ff35 - oversize
- Proof - "The Defense Commission Meets Twice a Week" 1940 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  moved from box 5, ff21D - oversize
- Working conditions (Box 64, Folder 3)
  moved from box 50, ff6 - oversize
- Ripped photograph of an arm and a voting machine (Box 64, Folder 4)
  moved from box 40, ff9
- People aboard a ship (Box 64, Folder 5)
  moved from box 30, ff1 - oversize
- ACWA. New York Joint Board Photos (Box 65, Folder 1)
  removed from mapcase 6/box 62
- Dinner Dance, Thirty-Second Annual Convention, American Federation of Hosiery Workers and New York Branch No. 130, Hotel Park Central - May 6, 1943 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  photo removed from panoramic boxes housed on top of mapcase
- pulled from mapcase 6/bx62 (Box 65)
- ACWA. New York Joint Board Photos (moved from mapcase 11) (Box 66)
- Images digitized from the collection. (Box 67)